Christy L. Willison

8 Swinderby Drive Oakwood Derby DE21 4RN

Email: Christy willison@hotmail.com

Tel: 07508628212

I am currently employed full time by Care UK as a Systems Specialist for Practice Plus, specializing in Emis primarily but will be taking on any new system that is incorporated along the way.

I also have my own Limited company where I take on any consultancy work where possible. I am passionate about technology and the use of software to enhance best working practice. I was previously a product specialist/clinical systems trainer at TPP. I am fully accredited in all systmone modules and have excellent knowledge and 6 years' experience of training. I have experience in system implementation and managing the projects from business change meetings to training the users and system configuration. I also have a lengthy back ground in clinical admin work and have had some experience in secretarial work. I am keen to learn and would be an asset to any employer.

I have great experience in both SystmOne and Emis Web. My most recent roles include configuration of templates/reports/letters etc over both systems.

Employment history

Current Permanent Employed Position

April 2019 - Present - Care UK - Practice Plus - Systems Specialist

I have been hired by Practice Plus to be their local Emis/Systems specialist. The role includes:

- Taking ownership of any system related issue
- Being the Emis expert for the organization
- Standardizing the use of emis across the Practice Plus sites, creating a scalable product that can be transferred easily when new practices come onboard.
- · Building in depth reports to support KPI's
- Building data entry templates to standardize coding.
- Learning new systems such as Docman 10, First Call and e24.
- Working with clinicians to adapt new ideas that will speed up local process' when using the different IT systems

Ongoing - Self employed Clinical Systems Specialist (roles below)

<u>January 2018 - Director - Leigh Training Solutions Itd</u> <u>IT consultant</u>

March 2019 - April 2019 - Embed Health - Clinical systems trainer

Role included:

- Running training workshops for GP practices within the CCG
- Revamping the organisations training programs and material
- Training on all areas of systmOne and Emis Web

August 2018- February 2019 - K2 Federation Hub Setup - Clinical Systems Consultant

I have recently finished a complete hub set up for the K2 Federation in Lincolnshire. My role included:

- Setting up the federations SystmOne hub from beginning to end.
- Setting up remote booking templates and applying monthly rotas.
- Training staff
- Creating documentation/user guides to support use of the hub.
- Running monthly reports and audits and manipulating data within Excel.

<u>July 2018- Present – Mitie Care and Custody – Clinical Systems Consultant</u>

I have recently finished 2 projects with Mitie. They asked me to do a whole redesign of their SystmOne use and follow up with training so that they could be self-sufficient. This was done for 2 contracts. My role includes:

- Analyzing their existing templates and creating a much slicker and streamlined process by creating protocols and easy to use templates.
- Optimizing the clinical system to reduce admin time for clinical staff. We found that by using the flow I had designed, working alongside a lead clinician, an average consultation in a custody suite went from 60mins to 15mins.
- Fully redesigning all templates/questionnaires/views/protocols to aid data entry.
- Successfully designing an easy to use, minimal training required product.
- Creating user guides and documentation to support the redesign.

<u>February 2018- December 31 2018- Senior system configuration analyst & facilitator - CWHHE - North West London collaboration</u>

I was hired on a contract basis for NHS North West London Collaboration of CCGS, working across 5 CCGs, I was responsible for:

- Standardising data entry templates across Emis and SystmOne.
- Building reports to marry up with the data from the templates
- Helping the systems development team with any problems with the clinical systems.
- Systmone and Emis web configuration of templates
- Working with clinicians to implement new changes and developments within the system I.e reports and data entry templates
- I have been heavily involved with building CCG wide reports for flu, shingles and the CQRS reports. These were rolled out across the North West London locality.
- I also dealt with service desk queries which involved sometimes trouble shooting over the phone and dialling into a users screen

February 2018 - Buisness Analyst - Brighton General Hospital

I worked here on a 4 day contract with the IT lead who wanted help in figuring out how to utilise Systmone to it's full potential and get it working for them. I also spent 2 days training him.

As a part of the business analysis I built templates, reports and letter templates for them. I also built protocols to help streamline they're workflows.

Previous Full Time Employment

May 2014 - January 2018

Product Specialist

TPP

As a product specialist I work, often, independently nationwide and internationally. I have been accredited in all systmone modules by TPP.

My skills include:

- Training
- Running train the trainer courses
- Demoing the system and selling to potential customers
- Business change
- Implementation of the system for new customers
- Data checking
- System configuration
- Building templates, protocols, reports
- Training non English speakers
- Demoing to non English speakers
- Public speaking
- Running talks as a part of the SNUG conference
- Preparing training sessions/demo's
- Working in my spare time
- Working with other trainers
- Writing training material
- Writing lesson plans and delegate assessments

December 2013- May 2014

Village Street Pharmacy

Village Medical Centre, Derby

I started here in early December 2013 as my employer could no longer provide over time. The pharmacist was keen to take me on and use my excellent IT skills to her advantage. I worked 12 hours a week running along side my existing job at the surgery.

My main duties include:

- Doing the cash up every morning from the previous days takings.
- Sending electronic prescription claims to the pricing authority
- Counting and filing prescriptions to ensure we are paid correctly for each prescription
- Taking orders and dealing with queries over the phone
- Logging all orders on the computer system

April 2010 - May 2013

Dr. Cotton and Partners, Village Surgery

Derby.

As one of the surgeries prescription clerks my role was deal with anything that comes into the surgery that is medication related.

My main duties included:

- Running off patients repeat prescription requests that came in, in a variety of different ways such as standard paper requests, online, fax or via systmone from other healthcare organisations.
- I also had to liaise with pharmacies and hospitals on a regular basis to ensure the patients were getting the right medication.
- Adding on new medications from the hospitals
 Calculating dose changes when patients had seen other healthcare professionals
- Working off my own initiative to try and decrease the GP's workload
- Training staff on the computer system
- I am also able to deal with difficult situations. Being in a job that deals with peoples medications it is imperative that we ensured patients safety and that people were not over using. I find I can

- speak to patients in a calming manor and diffuse a situation easily with the patient walking out happy.
- I also did a lot of the main reception jobs and had direct contact with the patients on a day to day basis be it over the phone or face to face. I had to deal with a lot of complicated queries and have been in situations where my actions could affect someone's health.
- Also during my time at Village I helped the practice with a change in computer system, I aided all staff with training and enjoyed doing so. I was also part of the practices pilot scheme on electronic prescribing. I have a very good grasp of this and helped other members of staff involved in the scheme to understand it and use it correctly and efficiently. I work at my best under pressure and enjoy being on the go.

September 2005 - April 2009

Dr. Doris and Partners, The Medical Centre

I worked here for four years. I started off as a part time filing clerk and worked my way up to a full time receptionist with various responsibilities. One of my main roles was training lesser confident members of staff on the computer system (systmone). I have a lot of patience and enjoy being able to help without passing judgment. I also stood in for the reception supervisor when she wasn't there, such as dealing with complaints on first contact and assisting my colleagues with difficult queries.

Other roles that I had was running off patients prescriptions, registering new/temporary patients and entering QOF data. I also have to restock the Drs. rooms with basic supplies, such as specimen bottles and needles. I also liaise with outside organizations relating to the role e.g. taking urgent blood results from the lab, social services, the P.C.T, and various others.

I was also trained up to do secretarial work such as audio typing and liaising with hospital in order to book appointments. This required great organizational skills. I have also gained an up to date first aid certificate and fire safety certificate.

March 2005 - Sept 2005

The Ferers Arms, Sinfin District Centre

Derby

I worked here as a barmaid, I really enjoyed it. I worked as a part of a small team, serving customers and working under pressure during busy periods. It was fast paced and sometimes the customers could become quite difficult, I had to try and diffuse a lot of awkward situations. I was also trusted with money and running the bar by myself during quieter periods.

Sept 2003 - July 2005 Marks and Spencer

<u>Derby.</u>

I worked here whilst doing my A-Levels at college, I worked cleaning the bakery and also as a janitor on a Sunday. I had to ensure that the bakery was cleaned to a very high standard and had to comply with basic health and safety measures.

Sept 2002 - Sept 2004

The Ragley Boatstop

Sinfin.

I worked here as a waitress, I had a lot of face to face contact with customers and worked as part of a busy team to ensure that customer satisfaction was to the highest standard and health and safety was a must

Education Wilmorton College 2004 - 2005 I attended the first year of the CACHE childcare course during which I obtained a basic first aid certificate, basic health and safety certificate and Key Skills level 2 in I.T. I also worked in various school settings with children between ages 3 and 7. I gave extra support to children with special needs. I have also done the receptionist course, P.R.P level 2.

Mackworth College 2002 - 2004

As - Levels

- Sociology D
- History D

A Levels

- English lang/lit D
- Psychology D

Sinfin Community School 1997 - 2002

• 9 GCSE's grades A –D

Reference's available on request